So how should we modify the code, so
طريقة تعديلنا لهذا الكود،
that list items have different background colors based on the category.
تضم أصناف القائمة ألوان خلفية مختلفة طبقًا لفئتها.
I'd like you to take a moment to think about your mental model
أود أن تفكر لوهلة بشأن نموذجك العقلي
of the Miwok app code base.
الخاص بأساس كود تطبيق "عملي".
Where could the background color information be stored?
أين يمكن تخزين معلومات لون الخلفية؟
Well, we could store it in all of these files.
حسنًا يمكننا تخزينها في جميع الملفات.
However, that would be an inefficient use of memory resources.
يعد ذلك استخدام غير كافي لموارد الذاكرة.
Remember that every variable takes up space in memory.
تذكر أن كل متغير يشغل مساحة في الذاكرة.
So to be a good citizen in Android, we should minimize the memory usage and
ومن أجل أن تكون على دراية بنظام آندرويد، عليك تقليل استخدام الذاكرة
store it in the minimal number of places where it's needed.
وتخزينها في أقل عدد من الأماكن بحسب الضرورة.
So this also minimizes the amount of places that know about this color.
يقلل ذلك أيضًا من عدد الأماكن التي تعرفها عن هذا اللون.
So should we show the color as a variable inside the Word class?
هل يجب أن نعرض اللون كمتغير داخل فئة النص.
Or maybe inside the WordAdapter class?
أو داخل فئة موائم النص؟
Or maybe inside each individual activity?
أو داخل النشاط الفردي؟
So take a look at the screenshots below and try to make your best educated guess
لنلق نظرة على لقطات الشاشة أدناه ونحاول التجربة لعمل أفضل تخمين
out of these three choices and then explain your reasoning below.
من بين هذه التخمينات الثلاثة وشرح أسبابك أدناها.